[{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983084270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":11393,"timeElapsed":2620288},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983093478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9206,"timeElapsed":2629497},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983108514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":15035,"timeElapsed":2644533},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983115756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7240,"timeElapsed":2651775},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983123865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8108,"timeElapsed":2659884},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983127933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4066,"timeElapsed":2663952},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983134238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6303,"timeElapsed":2670257},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983138985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4743,"timeElapsed":2675004},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983142127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3140,"timeElapsed":2678146},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983195205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":51500,"timeElapsed":2731224},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983202527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7321,"timeElapsed":2738546},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983206403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3874,"timeElapsed":2742422},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983208426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2022,"timeElapsed":2744445},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983211776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":2747795},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983223756,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11978,"timeElapsed":2759775},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983227864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4106,"timeElapsed":2763883},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983230691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":2766709},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983285490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":54798,"timeElapsed":2821509},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983294447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8954,"timeElapsed":2830465},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983305412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9610,"timeElapsed":2841431},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983308269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2855,"timeElapsed":2844288},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983310776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2505,"timeElapsed":2846795},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983314380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3601,"timeElapsed":2850399},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983317352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2970,"timeElapsed":2853371},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983325938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8584,"timeElapsed":2861956},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983332304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6365,"timeElapsed":2868323},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983335596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3290,"timeElapsed":2871614},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983338619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":2874638},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983345522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5773,"timeElapsed":2881541},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983349484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3961,"timeElapsed":2885503},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983352508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3020,"timeElapsed":2888527},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983358126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5617,"timeElapsed":2894145},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983372965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":14837,"timeElapsed":2908984},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983376348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3380,"timeElapsed":2912367},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983380129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3780,"timeElapsed":2916148},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983383200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3069,"timeElapsed":2919219},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983385223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2021,"timeElapsed":2921242},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983409496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":23107,"timeElapsed":2945515},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983411466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1969,"timeElapsed":2947485},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983450787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":39320,"timeElapsed":2986806},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983453081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":2989100},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983456227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":2992245},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983459324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3095,"timeElapsed":2995343},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983462788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3461,"timeElapsed":2998807},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983470488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7699,"timeElapsed":3006507},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983473077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2587,"timeElapsed":3009096},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983483230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8995,"timeElapsed":3019249},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983485735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2502,"timeElapsed":3021753},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983487380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1643,"timeElapsed":3023399},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983489847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2465,"timeElapsed":3025866},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983492001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":3028020},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983493377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1375,"timeElapsed":3029396},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983495341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1962,"timeElapsed":3031360},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983497103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1760,"timeElapsed":3033122},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983498962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":3034981},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983506987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6533,"timeElapsed":3043006},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983508724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":3044743},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983510657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":3046676},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983512301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1642,"timeElapsed":3048320},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983516135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3832,"timeElapsed":3052153},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983518534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2398,"timeElapsed":3054552},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983521204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2670,"timeElapsed":3057223},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983525536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4331,"timeElapsed":3061555},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983527043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"224","question":"If money was not an obstacle, where would you most like to travel? What would you do there?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1505,"timeElapsed":3063062},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983535561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7589,"timeElapsed":3071580},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983537331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":3073350},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983539483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":3075502},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983541030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1545,"timeElapsed":3077048},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983543520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2489,"timeElapsed":3079539},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983547532,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4011,"timeElapsed":3083551},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983550824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3290,"timeElapsed":3086843},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983553456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2630,"timeElapsed":3089475},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983555739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2282,"timeElapsed":3091758},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983557336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"186","question":"Come up with a new name for all seven days of the week based on how you feel about them (they can be made up words like “blesh” or use existing words like Boresday).","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1596,"timeElapsed":3093355},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983563534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5116,"timeElapsed":3099553},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983565198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1663,"timeElapsed":3101217},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983567498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2298,"timeElapsed":3103516},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983569514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2015,"timeElapsed":3105533},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983576739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7222,"timeElapsed":3112758},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983578450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":3114469},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983589466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":11015,"timeElapsed":3125485},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983593467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":3129486},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983597065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3596,"timeElapsed":3133084},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983620814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":22292,"timeElapsed":3156833},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983623283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":3159302},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983628410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5125,"timeElapsed":3164429},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983631719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3308,"timeElapsed":3167738},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983633994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2274,"timeElapsed":3170013},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983635829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":3171848},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983637434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1604,"timeElapsed":3173453},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983638703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1268,"timeElapsed":3174722},{"subjectID":"401y2hcyte","prolificID":"6765a8758e1a310fcc0dd9bd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b262c9e189f44da6fa1c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983640293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"193","question":"Do you play any instruments or did you play any growing up? Do you enjoy playing music?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1590,"timeElapsed":3176312}]